underarmour.co.uk 2015-12-04

# Under Armour | Privacy Policy

Here at Under Armour, we are committed to safeguarding your online privacy. To help us achieve our goal of providing the highest quality products and services, we use information from our interactions with you and other customers as well as from certain third parties. Because we respect your privacy, we have procedures to ensure that your personal information is handled in a responsible manner. We only share your personal information in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 and other applicable laws.

We have posted this Privacy Policy on our website to let you know what kind of information we collect, the purposes for which we collect and use the information, how it is handled, with whom it may be shared, and what choices you have regarding our use of your information.

You may contact Under Armour at any time with any privacy questions or concerns and to see the personal information you have given us or to request correction. For details of how to contact us, please see “ **How to contact us”**.

This Privacy Policy applies to the website [www.underarmour.co.uk](http://www.underarmour.co.uk/) owned by Under Armour Europe BV. Under Armour Europe BV is a multi-national organization, with legal entities, business processes, management structures, and technical systems that cross borders.

By using [www.underarmour.co.uk](http://www.underarmour.co.uk/) or through registration on the website, you entrust your personal data to Under Armour Europe BV and Under Armour, Inc. (Under Armour Europe BV’s parent company) and grant us permission to process your personal data that you have provided to us in accordance with the provisions of this Privacy Policy.

Under Armour Europe BV is located at: Olympisch Stadion 8 1076 DE Amsterdam Tel: +31 (0)20-715 5100

Under Armour, Inc. is located at: 1020 Hull Street Baltimore, Maryland USA 21230 Tel: +1-410-454-6649

Under Armour Europe BV and Under Armour, Inc. (hereinafter collectively referred to as: “Under Armour”) have jointly notified the Dutch Personal Data Authority regarding their processing of personal data.

You can jump to specific areas of our Privacy Policy by clicking on the links below or you can read on for our full Privacy Policy. For more information about our use of cookies and similar technology, please refer to our **[Cookie Policy](http://www.underarmour.co.uk/en-gb/cookie-policy.html)**.

## SECURITY AND REGISTRATION POLICIES

We go to great lengths to protect your personal information. We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), the industry-standard encryption technology to ensure that all of your personal and transactional information is protected to the highest standards over the Internet.

When the letters "http" in the URL change to "https," the "s" indicates you are in a secure area employing SSL. Your browser may also produce a pop-up message stating that you are about to enter or leave a secure area. Using a browser that is SSL capable will ensure that your information is encoded or encrypted when it is sent over the Internet.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet and no data storage can be 100% secure. Consequently, while we endeavor to safeguard your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure, we do not warrant or guarantee the absolute security of any personal information you transmit to, from or through our website.

We will notify you in the event we become aware of a security breach involving your personal information stored by or for us. By disclosing your email address to us for any reason, you _expressly consent_ to receive electronic notice from us in the event of such a security breach. If you believe that your account or any information you provided to us in no longer secure, please notify us immediately by using the email address or calling the phone number given in the **How to Contact Us** section below **.**

## WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DOES UNDER ARMOUR GATHER?

**Information You Submit To Us:** We receive and store any information you submit to us via our website or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our features. By simple usage of our website or through registration, you _grant us permission_ to process your personal data in accordance with the provisions of this Privacy Policy.

If you choose to register an account with us, we will collect, store and use information such as your name, e-mail address, postal address, and contact details. [www.underarmour.co.uk](http://www.underarmour.co.uk/) then keeps a record of this information. Additionally, you may have the option of providing information such as your gender, birth date, sports interests, shipping/billing address, daytime phone number, size and other information.

If you place an order with us, we will collect, store and use your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information, email address and phone number. [www.underarmour.co.uk](http://www.underarmour.co.uk/) then keeps a record of this information. For more information about how credit and debit card details are stored and used by [www.underarmour.co.uk](http://www.underarmour.co.uk/), please see “ ** _Security and Registration Policies_** ”.

**Automatic Information:** When you visit our website, we receive and store certain types of information through automatic data collection tools, including cookies, pixel tags, web beacons, embedded web links, and other commonly used information gathering tools. These tools collect certain standard information that your browser sends to our website such as your browser type and language, access times, IP-address, user-agent string and click stream behavior (i.e., the pages you view; the links you click; and other actions you take in connection with our website). Please see our **[Cookie Policy](http://www.underarmour.co.uk/en-gb/cookie-policy.html)** for more information about our use of cookies and pixel tags.

**Information From Other Sources:** If you have registered an account with us or placed an order through our website, to help us customize shopping for you, improve our communication with you, and improve our business overall, we may obtain certain demographic information about you from reputable third party sources. For example, in the event we determine that you live in a geographical area where the climate is usually cold and you have subscribed to receive email communications from us, we would be more likely to send you communications highlighting our ColdGear® product line rather than our HotGear® product line.

**Sensitive Personal Data:** Under Armour does not and will not register sensitive personal data concerning a person’s religion or philosophy of life, race, political persuasion, health and sexual life, or personal data concerning trade union membership.

## WHAT HAPPENS WHEN I REGISTER?

To make online shopping faster and easier, you may register with [_www.underarmour.co.uk_](http://www.underarmour.com/shop/uk/en). Using your email address and a password of your choice, you may access your account online at any time to add, delete or change information retained in your account.

We encourage users to create a registered account on our website. The benefit of having a registered account on [www.underarmour.co.uk](http://www.underarmour.co.uk/) is having the ability to view past orders and quickly access your shipping and billing information with a username and password. When you register with us as an online customer, we may ask for additional information such as what sports you play. We are not interested in collecting, and will not ask you to provide us with, sensitive personal data.

The alternative to having a registered account is visiting our website as a "Guest." As a Guest, you do not have access to past orders or the benefit of storing your billing and shipping information on our website.

## WHAT CAN I DO TO PROTECT MY PERSONAL INFORMATION?

Your account and personal information is protected by the password you provided when you created your [_www.underarmour.co.uk_](http://www.underarmour.com/) account. Always keep this password and login information private, and never share it with anyone. Ensure that you have up-to-date antivirus software.

Also, remember to sign off your account and close your browser window when you have finished your visit. This is to ensure that others cannot access your account, especially if you are sharing a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place such as a library or an Internet café. If you prefer to order by telephone, you may purchase online merchandise by calling 0080082766871. A member of our customer service team will gladly take your order.

If you are using a public computer, we strongly encourage you to close your browser at the conclusion of your session. Your information will still be stored with us but it will not be accessible to anyone else from that computer.

## WHY DOES UNDER ARMOUR COLLECT PERSONAL INFORMATION?

**Purposes Of Use:** We use the information that you provide to us via our website and through communication with you only for the following purposes:

  1. processing and fulfilling your order
  2. responding to your requests and your product inquiries
  3. for our own direct marketing purposes
  4. customizing future shopping for you
  5. improving our website
  6. communicating with you
  7. for our own financial accounting purposes.

** ** **Order Placement:** Once you decide to place an order, if you are not a registered customer, you will be given the option to register an account with our website or to place an order as a Guest. If you choose to become a registered customer, your personal information will be saved on our system to facilitate your future purchases on our website. Also, as a registered customer, you will have the ability to view your order history on our website.

On the other hand, if you choose to place the order as a Guest only, none of your personal information will be saved by us upon completion of your order except as may be reasonably necessary to document our business activities or as needed for required disclosures. Please see **_What happens when I register?_** for more information about your options to place an order as a registered customer or as a Guest.

We will send you an email message to confirm any order that you place on our website and when such order is shipped. Additionally, we may send you a reminder by email if you have left something in your shopping cart. Finally, we may send you an email inviting you to provide a rating and review of any product you purchase at our website. If you do not want to receive email messages or other communications from us, please see **_How does Under Armour use my information for direct marketing?_** for information about how to unsubscribe from our mailing list.

## HOW LONG DOES UNDER ARMOUR KEEP MY PERSONAL INFORMATION FOR?

The information, including but not limited to personal data detected with the tools mentioned in **_What Personal Information does Under Armour gather?_** , will only be stored on servers for the following purposes: statistical analyses, improvement of our website and the prevention or detection of fraud or abuse of our website.

Credit and debit card information is used only for payment processing and fraud prevention. Credit and debit card information is not used for any other purpose by Under Armour and will not be kept longer than necessary for providing the services.

## WHY DOES UNDER ARMOUR COLLECT INFORMATION FROM EMAIL?

To help us make email communication more useful and interesting, we may receive a confirmation when you open email messages from [_www.underarmour.co.uk_](http://www.underarmour.com/shop/uk/en) if your computer supports such capabilities. We also compare our customer list to lists received from other companies in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our customers. For more information, please see our **[Cookie Policy](http://www.underarmour.co.uk/en-gb/cookie-policy.html). **

If you do _not_ want to receive email messages or other mail from us, please see **_How Does Under Armour Use my Information for Direct Marketing?_** for information about how to unsubscribe from our mailing list.

## HOW DOES UNDER ARMOUR USE MY INFORMATION FOR DIRECT MARKETING?

Each registered customer has the choice of receiving announcements about our products and special events or promotions from us via email. You will receive promotional email messages from us only if you have agreed to receive them by:

  1. clicking in the box next to “Keep me in the loop for Under Armour news and promotions” when entering your shipping and billing information to place an order or when registering, or
  2. clicking on “Get email updates” at the top of the website home page and entering your email address.

## HOW DO I UNSUBSCRIBE FROM EMAIL COMMUNICATION FROM UNDER ARMOUR?

Each time you receive an email message from Under Armour, you will be given the opportunity to no longer receive email communication from Under Armour. You can unsubscribe from our mailing list by selecting the link "UNSUBSCRIBE" at the bottom of the email message. If you choose to unsubscribe, we will stop sending you email messages.

Please note, however, that some email promotions are prepared well in advance. We appreciate your patience in giving us time to carry out your request. Should you continue to receive email messages from us after unsubscribing, you may write to us about the continued use of your data for direct marketing purposes by using the email address or calling the phone number detailed in **_How to Contact Us_**.

If you would like more information about online marketing practices and to know your choices about not having this information used by our third party service providers, please click here [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) ** _._**

## DOES UNDER ARMOUR SHARE MY PERSONAL INFORMATION WITH OTHER PARTIES?

Information about our customers is an important part of our business. Under Armour does not sell its mailing list or customers’ email addresses or other information pertaining to its customers. We share customer information only as described below.

  1. **Third Party Service Providers:** We employ other companies (including our affiliates) and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and email, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance (including on-line advertising), providing search results and links, processing credit card payments and providing customer service. These third party service providers have access to customer personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use such information for any purpose other than the function which we have directed them to perform on our behalf. We require such third party service providers to implement and maintain reasonable security measures to safeguard the confidentiality, security and integrity of your personal information.
  2. **Merger, Acquisition, Sale/Transfer Of Assets Or Business:** If our company is acquired by or merged with or into another entity, or if our assets or business is sold or transferred to another entity, your personal information may be transferred to such entity as part of the transaction, and that entity and its affiliates may use your personal information under the terms of this Privacy Policy.
  3. **Protection Of Under Armour and Others:** Except for the purposes as described above, we will not share the personal data you provide to Under Armour with any third parties without your permission, unless to: (i) respond to duly authorised information requests of governmental authorities; (ii) comply with any law, regulation, subpoena, or court order; (iii) help prevent fraud or to enforce or protect the rights and properties of Under Armour or its subsidiaries; or (iv) protect the personal safety of Under Armour employees and third parties on Under Armour property. This also means that we will not share any information in your account (in ways other than described in this Privacy Policy) to assist any search engine, software, service, or any other system that delivers advertisements, messages, or other information to you as an Under Armour user, without your explicit, prior approval for such sharing. At any time, you may change your mind and revoke this permission.

## CAN I ACCESS AND UPDATE MY PERSONAL INFORMATION?

You have a right to access your personal information. If you are a registered customer, you may exercise this right by visiting the " **[My Account](http://www.underarmour.co.uk/en-gb/my-account)** " section of our website. From this link, you can view, update or delete certain of your personal information from our database.

If you wish to edit personal information but are unable to do so by visiting the " **[My Account](http://www.underarmour.co.uk/en-gb/my-account)** " section of our website, please visit 

and select **_Contact Us_**.

If you are not a registered customer but wish to contact us about accessing any personal information retained by us, please visit [_www.underarmour.co.uk_](http://www.underarmour.com/shop/uk/en) and select **_Contact Us_**.

## CAN I OBJECT TO CERTAIN DATA PROCESSING AND DO I HAVE THE RIGHT OF REVOCATION?

**Right to object:** You have the right to object if the processing of your personal is not necessary for the legitimate interests of Under Armour or a third party. You can register an objection on the basis of this ground in connection with your particular personal circumstances by using the following email address: **[feedback-uk@underarmour.com](mailto:feedback-uk@underarmour.com)**.

**Right of revocation:** You may at any time request that we delete your personal data or refrain from using it to contact you. You may also at any time request that we delete the account you have created and activated during online registration. You may communicate such requests by sending an email to us at **[feedback-uk@underarmour.com](mailto:feedback-uk@underarmour.com)** detailing what information you wish to be deleted. Please note that data which are absolutely essential for processing an outstanding order will not be affected by any deletions you make or request. Bear in mind however that our personalized service relies on the personal data you provide. If you revoke your permission for the use of your personal data, then we will no longer be able to provide this personalized service to you.

## HOW CAN I SEE THE PERSONAL INFORMATION UNDER ARMOUR HOLDS ON ME?

You have the right to see the personal data that we hold on you by sending a written request to: [**feedback-uk@underarmour.com**](mailto:feedback-uk@underarmour.com).  We aim to deal with all enquiries promptly.We charge a £10 fee to meet our costs in providing this information to you.

Once we receive your request, we may request additional information to confirm your identity and will send you details of how to pay the £10 processing fee. We will then provide you with an electronic file of all the information we hold about you as soon as we can and in any event within 40 days from you paying the fee.

## DOES UNDER ARMOUR LINK TO THIRD PARTY WEBSITES?

Our website may contain links to certain third-party websites. Under Armour does not own, control or operate such linked websites, and is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of such linked websites. The personal data you choose to provide to or that is collected by these third parties is not covered by our website’s Privacy Policy. Privacy policies and practices for such linked websites may differ from our Privacy Policy and practices. Your access and use of such linked websites is entirely and solely at your own risk. We urge you to read the privacy policies of such linked websites before disclosing your personal information on such websites.

## HOW OFTEN DOES UNDER ARMOUR CHANGE ITS PRIVACY POLICY?

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time without prior notice. You can determine when this Policy was last revised by referring to **_When Was The Privacy Policy Last Updated?_**. Any changes to our policy will become effective upon posting of the revised Privacy Policy on the Internet, accessible through [_www.underarmour.co.uk_](http://www.underarmour.com/shop/uk/en) **.**

We encourage you to bookmark this page and to periodically review it to ensure familiarity with the most current version of our Privacy Policy. If you are a registered customer, we may notify you of any changes to our privacy policy via email and may ask you to affirmatively acknowledge consent to the changes (e.g., by checking a box or clicking a button) at the time of your next account login on our website.

## A SPECIAL NOTE TO PARENTS:

Under Armour takes the privacy of children seriously. Our website is not directed at children, we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13 through our website and we request that children under the age of 13 not submit any personal information through our website.

## SAFE HARBOR CERTIFICATION OF UNDER ARMOUR, INC.

If you choose to provide us with personal contact information, **_you consent_** to the transfer, processing and storage of that information on Under Armour, Inc’s servers located in the United States.  
Under Armour, Inc. complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. The Safe Harbor certification is specific to Under Armour, Inc., other Under Armour subsidiaries and affiliates are not covered by this certification (e.g., MapMyFitness, Inc.). Under Armour, Inc. has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement.

To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Under Armour, Inc.’s certification, please visit [**www.export.gov/safeharbor**](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor) ** _._**

In compliance with the US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles, Under Armour, Inc. commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information.  
European Union or Swiss citizens with inquiries or complaints regarding this Privacy Policy should in the first instance contact:

Under Armour, Inc.  
1020 Hull Street  
Baltimore, Maryland 21230  
USA  
Tel: +1-410-454-6649  
Email: **[feedback-us@underarmour.com](mailto:feedback-us@underarmour.com).**

Under Armour, Inc. has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint by using the contact details listed above, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed by Under Armour, Inc., please visit the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR website at [**www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints**](http://www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints) for more information and to file a complaint.

## HOW TO CONTACT US

We value your opinions. If you have any questions, comments or concerns concerning this Privacy Policy or about our handling of personal information relating to you, please click here [_www.underarmour.co.uk_](http://www.underarmour.com/shop/uk/en) and click Contact Us or use the following address, phone number or e-mail address:

Under Armour, Inc.  
1020 Hull Street  
Baltimore, Maryland 21230  
USA  
Tel: +1-410-454-6649  
Email: [**feedback-us@underarmour.com**](mailto:feedback-us@underarmour.com)

## WHEN WAS THE PRIVACY POLICY LAST UPDATED?

August 27, 2014
